wisdomfordominion.com 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy | Wisdom for Dominion

Wisdom for Dominion is aware that you care about your privacy. How your information is been used and shared. We hope the following statements will help understand how we collect, use and protect the information you provide to us.

## What we collect and how we use it.

  * ### Information You Provide

When you sign up for an account on our site by registering, we ask you for personal information. Such will include your name, email address, country and an account password. We use the information you provide to improve the quality of your experience with our services.

  * ### Cookies

When you visit our site, we send cookies to your computer so we can uniquely identify your browser. Accepting our cookies allows you to keep your user preferences from one session to another. Although most browsers support cookies, you can disable this.

## How do we use your information?

We do not use your information in any way for benefits or otherwise as of now. But if we were to make such uses, we will definitely require your approval before going on. So your email addresses are not sold to any third party body. They maybe enlisted on our newsletter permitting you to receive notifications on new content uploaded to the site.

## How do we protect your information?

Wisdom for Dominion does not share your information with other institutions outside of Wisdom for Dominion. We may share your personal information if and only if it has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to:

(a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.

(b) enforce applicable Terms Of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof.

(c) detect, prevent, and address fraud, security or technical issues, or

(d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Wisdom for Dominion, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. We take appropriate security measures to protect your information against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. Unless explicit permission is obtained from you, Wisdom for Dominion restricts access to personal information to it’s contractors and agents who may need to know that information to operate, develop or improve our platform. As such these individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination, if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Data Integrity

Wisdom for Dominion ensures that it collects only the information which is necessary for enhancing and promoting our services. We however depend on our users to guarantee the integrity of the information we receive as we permit you update and modify your information when necessary.

## Accessing and updating personal information

When you use Wisdom for Dominion, we make good efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate service purposes. We require individual users to identify themselves as explicitly as possible so as to ease interactions in our community.

## Enforcements

Wisdom for Dominion periodically reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints regarding privacy issues, it is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We reserve the right to kick out any  users who are not in compliance with our Privacy Policy or who otherwise jeopardize the freedom and liberty of usage of any other user.

## Questions

Any questions about our privacy policy should be directed to: [legal@wisdomfordominion.com](mailto:legal@youversion.com)
